Ward One has privileges,
endless supplies, and patience
with food check marks.
Thankfully, George has a friend.
So Noa, Noa, Noa.
I was thinking maybe
we should hang out sometime.
Dinner?
Something spicy.
Um, food-food?
[CHUCKLES] I'm just eating
whatever fits in my pocket.
Well, I am known for my
protein-forward pesto chicken.
Wait, w-what are you doing?
Oh, um...
Yeah, you got to train
the obliques.
[GROANS]
Side plank the soul.
Uh, definitely a yellow flag.
So, you want to touch this?
No, no. [CHUCKLES]
Don't worry.
Most people ask.
You're lucky.
[CHUCKLES] Red flag! Red flag!
What?
So, uh, dinner? Thursday?
Oh, I'm allergic...
To food?
To everything
that just happened.
JC's coming for Ward Five.
You're going to be busy.
[CHUCKLES]
It's the perks of Ward One.
[SMOOCHES]
I'd do him.
[GROANS]
This JC thing?
That's trouble.
Excuse me.
Back in my time,
guys would sing for me
and ask for the
parents' blessings.
[CHUCKLES] You should've
hit him where it counts!
- Is that how Mr. Tess got you?
- No!
Eyes forward, Noa.
You look like you're talking
to yourself again.
Got any intel?
Yeah, the Latino ghost
heard whispers,
joint commission, our Ward.
I didn't hear anything.
Uh, we have a lot of
gossips floating around.
That's impossible!
We've hit all of our marks.
JC's no joke, dear.
They don't just do
unannounced visits.
- [WIND HOWLING]
- [LIGHTS FLICKERING]
D-Did you feel that?
Okay, that's new.
What's wrong?
I'm okay, dear.
Go see Jane.
- [WIND HOWLING]
- [LIGHTS FLICKERING]
[JANE] Relax.
I would've been flagged
if they were on site.
Are you sure?
Is there not someone
we can call?
We all have our connections,
Noa.
You just have to know
who bought who dinner.
[DIALING, LINE RINGING]
Hey, you.
It's me.
I know. I miss you too.
No, I can't. I'm married now.
Anywho, quick ask.
Is JC supposed to be
at the hospital today?
I know it's a silly question.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
What do you mean
their flight was delayed?
Alright everyone,
we have a few hours,
but that's more than
enough time.
I mean,
look at what we've built.
Now let's show them
who we are.
Okay, throw the SOPs at me.
I will skim them emotionally
and somehow know everything.
Zero OSHA violations, people.
Fix, repair, tape all signage.
All rooms will have flowers.
They're sponsored by me.
Don't use your phones.
HIPAA matters.
Dust, I kill you.
Crap, I'm nice.
Here's 20, clean more.
(In Latin)
Talk to all the ghosts,
I don't want
any hauntings today.
And you, don't you have
anything to do?
We got this, Noa.
Has anyone seen Grim?
He's scheduled today.
No, I haven't seen him.
Do you need help
with medication?
Oh! I'm okay. Thank you.
Oh! Just make sure
those records are up to date.
- Okay.
- On it.
Let's take a breath
before anyone accuses
anyone of anything.
You were there!
You heard him make that threat.
I will not have you
walking around here
besmirching my name, Jane.
Besmirching?
[PAPERS SCATTER]
I got you besmirching
right here, mother--
- Oh, hey-- Security!
- What you got, Walt?
- What's up?
- Hold on.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[MOP THUDS]
They're here.
Early.
Are we dead?
Looks like Mariah Carey
threw up Christmas in here.
I didn't raise a coward.
[EXHALES] We got this.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Complaint 39.
Requirement for staff
to communicate
in a non-English language.
What? No, I would never.
Excuse me.
Actually...
per Joint Commission
communication standard
RI.01.01.03,
staff are allowed
to speak another language
if it helps facilitate
patient comprehension.
(In Filipino)
So, thank you very much!
You speak Filipino?
Ros forces me to learn it
because I get lost a lot.
[GASPS]
Noted.
- [SPRAY HISSES]
- Trust me, darling.
Those will kill you.
Do you like the flowers?
They're fresh.
Hello?
Did you hear me?
Complaint 5517.
Potential contamination risk
due to unsecured
open beverage on
a patient care surface.
I literally just walked
through this room!
Get the EVS!
I'm not going to get cited
just because of a cup.
I'm going to post about this.
That wasn't there earlier.
- [WIND HOWLING]
- [EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Who are you?
[MUSIC TURNS SUSPENSEFUL]
- [MUSIC STOPS]
- [BEEPS]
Hello.
I'm trying to pull up
the patient complaints
for Ward Five.
The dashboard
isn't showing anything.
[WOMAN] And what seems
to be the issue?
It's blank.
Zero complaints for months.
There are no complaints.
Why the hell is JC here?
Please hold.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINE DISCONNECTS]
Hello?
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EXHALES]
It smells weird in here.
Strawberries.
I need to verify an item
reported on Rack 7B.
Hmm.
Expired.
[WRITING]
That wasn't supposed
to be there.
I didn't have time to finish
checking all the cabinets.
[SIGHS] This is all my fault.
I should have let the CNA help.
No, Noa.
Someone told her.
[GRUNTS]
This is where it all
began for you, isn't it?
What are you?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
How many breaths
did you try to steal
before your body just...
gave up?
Whatever you are,
let me help my daughter.
Do forgive my bedside manner.
My presence means
the message is overdue.
You're an Archangel?
Clever girl.
You do rise marginally
above the rabble.
Where's Grim?
You remember what he told you
a few months back?
Every rule shattered
demands its due.
That's how it works.
That's the truth.
Then I'll pay it.
Because we allow it.
You're not an angel.
You're a demon!
Demon! Demon!
[MUFFLED SPEAKING]
Do be careful
with my feelings, darling.
He has permitted patience.
I'm not.
But you...
I know you.
Hard hands.
Harsher words.
I love yous.
Rationed like wartime sugar.
It's no mystery
she's glued to you.
Children crave what
they're starved of.
[MUFFLED SPEAKING]
- [MUFFLED SPEAKING]
- Hmm.
Don't pout, Tessy Tess.
All those secrets you hoarded.
You fed her.
You clothed her.
Yet you never told her.
[MUFFLED SPEAKING]
And you had decades.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
[ARTHUR] Yo! N-n-n-Noa!
Could this day get any worse?
[GRUNTING]
Told you they were coming.
How did you know?
Oh, dude.
Let me tell you over dinner.
You still allergic?
What?
[ARTHUR] To Thursday?
To dates?
With me?
[GEORGE] Hey.
What's going on here?
[ARTHUR] Oh, bro.
It's all good. It's gravy.
We're just scheduling
our date for Thursday.
[GRUNTS]
God, what?
Even your jaw's ripped?
Oh, yeah.
Thirty minutes a day
of chewing gum.
- Okay.
- Straight sets.
George, don't give me
any more problems today.
I'm not. I just...
He was smiling weird
and you looked sad and...
I got scared.
[ARTHUR] You do have great
wrist alignment though.
Yeah.
- Thanks, man.
- Okay.
Stop complimenting violence!
And...
you're on for Thursday.
Ha! Yes!
Stoked. You're going
to love my pesto.
You got a great swing, buddy.
[CHUCKLES]
[SCOFFS]
What was that about?
Intel.
I hate secrets.
Today was a disaster, huh?
Pretty much.
You okay?
[NOA] You don't strike me
as the violent type.
Shouldn't have been
hitting on you.
[NOA CHUCKLES FAINTLY]
I just mean, you don't deserve
to get cornered
on top of everything else today.
Come on.
Let's head inside.
We need to post-mortem.
[JAY] Hi.
I got your messages...
your emails...
and screenshots.
We don't get the results of
the visit for a couple of days.
Maybe they'll pass.
You're not that stupid, Jay.
Noa's only had
a couple of months
to whip this place into shape,
and she's done a good job.
[JAY] Lady, don't do that.
Do what?
I've had your back since
day one, and you know this.
You don't understand.
I do.
We're in the business of caring.
It's okay to care.
When I was a surgical resident,
we had a boy who was gone.
My attending said it.
He wouldn't survive.
But I was stubborn.
This isn't about you.
[JAY] Let me finish.
After the first operation,
he sank.
So I rolled him back in.
Scalpel.
Suction.
Stitch.
I cut until the anatomy frayed.
I cut until his skin curled
like paper.
So what?
You'd let him die?
At some point you
have to ask yourself,
when is caring too much?
This was targeted!
[JAY] Even if it was.
If you keep pouring blood
in a limb you can't save...
you'll bleed out the whole body.
Judas.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GEORGE] Hey.
We almost finished taking down
the decorations
they complained about.
[SIGHS]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
They didn't wait
for the full report.
This was already decided.
The board is closing Ward Five.
Like for renovation?
[JANE] Closure.
Patients to be reassigned
within 48 hours.
- Staff--
- No!
They can't just transfer us.
This is the only work
I've ever actually enjoyed.
Or tolerated.
I'd be crying if
my tear ducts worked.
I'm fired, aren't I?
That's impossible.
They can't fire the person
holding it together.
I've met a lot of
divas and directors,
and she's the first leader
I've had
who didn't make it
about herself.
I'm so sorry.
Excuse me.
[NOA EXHALES SHARPLY]
[NOA] You all did
everything you could.
But this is on me.
Go home.
You deserve some rest.
Please.
- Noa.
- Boss.
Let's give her
a second to breathe.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[PLATE BREAKS]
[TESS] Witch!
I've been a nurse in LA
for 30 years.
Meth heads, crackheads,
spoiled Hollywood nepo babies.
Do you really think
I'm scared of you?
I know why
you can't drag me out.
You need me to
walk away on my own.
But my God gives me that choice.
[YOLANDA] Hm.
You think you know better?
I'm an Archangel.
So was Lucifer!
Take one step, Tess!
And I'll make sure
you regret it.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
You're not giving up, are you?
Oh, I don't have time for this.
- Just sit. One second, Noa.
- I have to go.
- One second, Noa. Noa, Noa!
- Give me my stuff back!
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
What was that?
Ugh, I don't know.
[NOA SIGHS]
It's pretty weak.
Just like that punch.
Arthur, really?
I mean, you think he has
the brain capacity for
that information?
I don't know.
Not knowing things just
makes me feel like...
Pissed.
I don't want to think
about anything tonight.
You don't have to.
Well, at least you have
a girlfriend to go home to.
Actually...
we broke up.
She felt tired of
having to compete.
[NOA GASPS]
- Oh, I'm so sorry.
- Don't be.
I'm fired, anyway.
[TESS] Jesus Christ!
Ew! Why him?
I don't like your pairing.
I'm sorry. Did I do something?
George, that wasn't
supposed to happen.
Um...
Do you know what
I've been through today?
You? Really?
Noa, who are you talking to?
George, can you please get out?
- But I--
- George, please!
[NOA SCOFFS]
You have a lot of
explaining to do.
Where have you been?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Tess, you're coming with me!
What are you?
You selfish little girl!
You're the reason she insists on
staying where
she doesn't belong.
Please! Stop!
No!
Get off her!
Please!
She's all I have!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
All you have.
Oh!
You don't know.
Don't!
She's not all you have!
What about your daddy?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You don't know
about Pacoima, do you?
[TESS] Dear!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]